text,entity_text,entity_label,entity_category,is_well_known
"Transfer $5000 from John Doe to account 123-456-789 at DBS Bank","DBS Bank","ORG","Bank",TRUE
"Transfer $5000 from John Doe to account 123-456-789 at DBS Bank","John Doe","PERSON","Customer",TRUE
"Transfer $5000 from John Doe to account 123-456-789 at DBS Bank","5000","MONEY","Amount",TRUE
"Payment received from Twitter for advertising services rendered","Twitter","ORG","Social Media Company",TRUE
"Invoice issued to Temasek Polytechnic for training services","Temasek Polytechnic","ORG","Educational Institution",FALSE
"Customer feedback from National University of Singapore alumni program","National University of Singapore","ORG","University",TRUE
"Wire transfer to OCBC Bank account for property purchase","OCBC Bank","ORG","Bank",TRUE
"Payment to Grab Holdings for employee transportation allowance","Grab Holdings","ORG","Tech Company",TRUE
"Remittance to Nanyang Technological University scholarship fund","Nanyang Technological University","ORG","University",TRUE
"Transaction with Singapore General Hospital for medical insurance claim","Singapore General Hospital","ORG","Hospital",TRUE
"Transfer to Ministry of Manpower for work permit fees","Ministry of Manpower","ORG","Government Agency",TRUE
"Payment from Shopee Singapore for merchant settlement","Shopee Singapore","ORG","E-commerce Company",TRUE
"Invoice to Tong Eng Brothers Pte Ltd for construction materials","Tong Eng Brothers Pte Ltd","ORG","Construction Company",FALSE
"Payment received from Haw Par Corporation for consulting fees","Haw Par Corporation","ORG","Pharmaceutical Company",FALSE
"Transfer to Breadtalk Group for catering services","Breadtalk Group","ORG","Food & Beverage Company",FALSE
"Remittance to Tan Tock Seng Hospital for medical treatment","Tan Tock Seng Hospital","ORG","Hospital",TRUE
"Payment to Singapore Polytechnic for course enrollment","Singapore Polytechnic","ORG","Educational Institution",TRUE
"Wire transfer from Sea Limited for software licensing","Sea Limited","ORG","Tech Company",TRUE
"Transaction with Changi General Hospital emergency services","Changi General Hospital","ORG","Hospital",TRUE
"Payment to Institute of Technical Education for vocational training","Institute of Technical Education","ORG","Educational Institution",TRUE
"Transfer from PropertyGuru Pte Ltd for advertising partnership","PropertyGuru Pte Ltd","ORG","Real Estate Tech Company",FALSE
"Invoice to Razer Inc for gaming hardware procurement","Razer Inc","ORG","Tech Company",TRUE
"Payment to Singapore Management University executive program","Singapore Management University","ORG","University",TRUE
"Remittance to Kwong Wai Shiu Hospital for charitable donation","Kwong Wai Shiu Hospital","ORG","Hospital",FALSE
"Transfer to Lazada Singapore for e-commerce services","Lazada Singapore","ORG","E-commerce Company",TRUE
"Payment from RedMart by Lazada for grocery delivery","RedMart by Lazada","ORG","Retail Company",FALSE
"Wire transfer to NTUC FairPrice for corporate bulk purchase","NTUC FairPrice","ORG","Retail Company",TRUE
"Transaction with Facebook Singapore for digital marketing","Facebook Singapore","ORG","Social Media Company",TRUE
"Payment to Google Asia Pacific for cloud services","Google Asia Pacific","ORG","Tech Company",TRUE
"Transfer to Amazon Web Services for infrastructure hosting","Amazon Web Services","ORG","Tech Company",TRUE
"Invoice issued to Keppel Corporation for marine engineering","Keppel Corporation","ORG","Industrial Company",TRUE
"Payment from SingTel for telecommunications services","SingTel","ORG","Telecommunications Company",TRUE
"Remittance to StarHub for mobile plan subscription","StarHub","ORG","Telecommunications Company",TRUE
"Transfer to M1 Limited for corporate data plan","M1 Limited","ORG","Telecommunications Company",TRUE
"Payment to Certis Cisco for security services","Certis Cisco","ORG","Security Services Company",TRUE
"Wire transfer from CapitaLand for property management fees","CapitaLand","ORG","Real Estate Company",TRUE
"Transaction with Mapletree Logistics Trust for warehouse rental","Mapletree Logistics Trust","ORG","Real Estate Investment Trust",TRUE
"Payment to ComfortDelGro for corporate transportation","ComfortDelGro","ORG","Transportation Company",TRUE
"Transfer to SMRT Corporation for transit services","SMRT Corporation","ORG","Transportation Company",TRUE
"Invoice to Sheng Siong Group for supermarket supplies","Sheng Siong Group","ORG","Retail Company",FALSE
"Payment from Great Eastern Holdings for insurance settlement","Great Eastern Holdings","ORG","Insurance Company",TRUE
"Remittance to AIA Singapore for life insurance premium","AIA Singapore","ORG","Insurance Company",TRUE
"Transfer to Prudential Singapore for investment plan","Prudential Singapore","ORG","Insurance Company",TRUE
"Payment to Koufu Group for food court rental","Koufu Group","ORG","Food & Beverage Company",FALSE
"Wire transfer from Yeo Hiap Seng for beverage distribution","Yeo Hiap Seng","ORG","Food & Beverage Company",FALSE
"Transaction with Old Chang Kee for franchise fees","Old Chang Kee","ORG","Food & Beverage Company",FALSE
"Payment to Ya Kun Kaya Toast for catering services","Ya Kun Kaya Toast","ORG","Food & Beverage Company",FALSE
"Transfer to Toast Box for franchise agreement","Toast Box","ORG","Food & Beverage Company",FALSE
"Invoice issued to Khong Guan Biscuit Factory for supplies","Khong Guan Biscuit Factory","ORG","Food Manufacturing Company",FALSE
"Payment from Netflix Singapore for content licensing","Netflix Singapore","ORG","Entertainment Company",TRUE
"Remittance to Spotify Singapore for music streaming subscription","Spotify Singapore","ORG","Entertainment Company",TRUE
"CEO Helen Wong announced OCBC Bank quarterly earnings report","Helen Wong","PERSON","CEO",TRUE
"CEO Helen Wong announced OCBC Bank quarterly earnings report","OCBC Bank","ORG","Bank",TRUE
"Customer Robert Tan submitted housing loan application","Robert Tan","PERSON","Customer",TRUE
"Account manager Alice Lim processed wire transfer request","Alice Lim","PERSON","Employee",TRUE
"Beneficiary Mary Chen received remittance payment","Mary Chen","PERSON","Customer",TRUE
"Director Tan Chong Meng approved credit facility","Tan Chong Meng","PERSON","Executive",TRUE
"Transfer amount SGD 10000.00 credited to savings account","10000.00","MONEY","Amount",TRUE
"Account balance S$2500 as of statement closing date","2500","MONEY","Amount",TRUE
"Payment of USD 5000 for international wire transfer","5000","MONEY","Amount",TRUE
"Invoice total $15000.50 payable within 30 days","15000.50","MONEY","Amount",TRUE
"Credit card charge SGD 450.75 at merchant outlet","450.75","MONEY","Amount",TRUE
"Loan disbursement S$250000 for property purchase","250000","MONEY","Amount",TRUE
"Payment due on 15-Jan-2025 for outstanding invoice","15-Jan-2025","DATE","Transaction Date",TRUE
"Transaction completed on 01/10/2024 at branch office","01/10/2024","DATE","Transaction Date",TRUE
"Statement period from 01-Sep-2024 to 30-Sep-2024","01-Sep-2024","DATE","Period Start",TRUE
"Statement period from 01-Sep-2024 to 30-Sep-2024","30-Sep-2024","DATE","Period End",TRUE
"Loan maturity date 31-Dec-2030 for mortgage facility","31-Dec-2030","DATE","Maturity Date",TRUE
"Direct debit scheduled for 5th of every month","5th","DATE","Recurring Date",TRUE
"Wire transfer to Thailand Krung Thai Bank beneficiary","Thailand","GPE","Country",TRUE
"Wire transfer to Thailand Krung Thai Bank beneficiary","Krung Thai Bank","ORG","Bank",FALSE
"Remittance from Singapore to Malaysia recipient account","Singapore","GPE","Country",TRUE
"Remittance from Singapore to Malaysia recipient account","Malaysia","GPE","Country",TRUE
"Payment to vendor in Hong Kong for trade finance","Hong Kong","GPE","Country",TRUE
"Customer residing at 123 Orchard Road Singapore 238858","Orchard Road","LOC","Street",TRUE
"Customer residing at 123 Orchard Road Singapore 238858","Singapore","GPE","Country",TRUE
"Branch located at Raffles Place financial district","Raffles Place","LOC","Location",TRUE
"Transaction at Marina Bay Sands integrated resort","Marina Bay Sands","FAC","Facility",TRUE
"Account opened at Changi Business Park branch","Changi Business Park","LOC","Location",TRUE
"Payment to Indonesia for import trade settlement","Indonesia","GPE","Country",TRUE
"Transfer from United States correspondent bank","United States","GPE","Country",TRUE
